David Jex

1343 Bandera Hwy Kerrville, TX 78028

Phone: (256)738-0090 E-Mail: david.jex@me.com Personal Site: rex725.github.io GitHub: github.com/rex725

Objective

Fullscript PHP and Javascript Developer transitioning from 4 years in Software Analysis. Has a love for problem solving and creating a clean and interesting UI. Currently building an all in one Dungeons and Dragons application to hone skills.

Experience

Courier/Jaguar Logistics

08/2016-04-2017

 Maintained a strict schedule, and HIPPA compliancy while picking up and delivering sensitive specimens for medical lab testing.

Greenway Analyst/Peterson Health

05/2016-04/2014

- Maintained PrimeSuite for 12 clinics consisting 30 physicians as well as supporting staff.
- Implemented a bi-directional interface with the hospital EMR Meditech.
- Created a query to pull out referrals created and export them to a drop box to be picked up by another vendor.
- Worked with vendors to meet deadlines for implementing new functionality and upgrades such as implementing Medfusion, Direct Messaging, Immunization Registries, and the Specialty Registry.
- Developed workflows for better utilization of PrimeSuite including editing templates and working with the staff to develop better processes.
- Developed reports for recording financial, patient, and practice data.

Implementation Specialist/Greenway Health

04/2014-08/2012

- Managed teams to implement PrimeSuite for hospital and large private practices.
- Provided training for physicians and support staff on how to use PrimeSuite efficiently.

Education

Codeup/San Antonio, TX

2017

Codeup is an immersive, fullstack career accelerator that provides students with 536+ hours of expert instruction in software development.

BYU Idaho (Online)/Rexburg, Idaho

2016-Present

Currently working on a degree in Software Engineering.

Skills	• PHP	• Linux
 Javascript 	• MySQL	• HTML
• JQuery	• Scrum	• CSS
• React	• Laravel	